<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>SA Info</title>
    <link>https://salocal.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SA Info</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://salocal.info/img/logo/logo.svg</url>
      <link>https://salocal.info/img/logo/logo.svg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 20:22:50 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://salocal.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>South African E-Wallets Help SRD Recipients Receive Funds</title>
      <link>https://salocal.info/za/sassa/south-african-e-wallets-help-srd-recipients-receive-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 20:22:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://salocal.info/za/sassa/south-african-e-wallets-help-srd-recipients-receive-funds/</guid>
      <description>Discover the benefits of digital wallets and how to fast-track payments for COVID-19 SRD. E-wallets and Cash Send services can help you receive funds easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SASSA Grant requirements you need to know</title>
      <link>https://salocal.info/za/sassa/sassa-grant-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 21:40:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://salocal.info/za/sassa/sassa-grant-requirements/</guid>
      <description>SASSA provides grants to South Africans that cannot provide for themselves. Here&amp;#39;s a list of all the grants and the requirements to apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driving Licence Card Online Renewal</title>
      <link>https://salocal.info/za/license/driving-licence-card-online-renewal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:37:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://salocal.info/za/license/driving-licence-card-online-renewal/</guid>
      <description>Book your driving licence renewal online for Gauteng and Eastern Cape residents. Driving licence card renewal process and everything you will need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Africans set to tighten their budgets once again as fuel and inflation increases</title>
      <link>https://salocal.info/za/finance/inflation-south-africa-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 20:20:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://salocal.info/za/finance/inflation-south-africa-2022/</guid>
      <description>Here’s the latest fuel prices as of July 2022. South Africans are set to tighten their budgets once again as inflation reaches an all time high of 7.4% in June 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update to the SRD Grant as of July 2022</title>
      <link>https://salocal.info/za/sassa/update-to-srd-grant-july-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 06:59:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://salocal.info/za/sassa/update-to-srd-grant-july-2022/</guid>
      <description>The Minister of the Department of Social Development (DSD) has submitted draft regulations to amend some of the strict requirements for the SRD Grant as more than half of applicants are rejected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Flightless Birds of the Cape Peninsula</title>
      <link>https://salocal.info/travel/the-flightless-birds-of-the-cape-peninsula/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 18:24:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://salocal.info/travel/the-flightless-birds-of-the-cape-peninsula/</guid>
      <description>Explore Cape Town, take a guided tour to enjoy all the activities from the Cape Point Ostrich Farm to the must-see Penguin colony on Boulders Beach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City of Cape Town Traffic Fine Payment Changes</title>
      <link>https://salocal.info/za/fines/city-of-cape-town-traffic-fine-payment-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 22:34:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://salocal.info/za/fines/city-of-cape-town-traffic-fine-payment-changes/</guid>
      <description>The City has announced payment and provider changes for traffic fines as of July 2022. Here’s how to pay your traffic fines online or via shopping stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://salocal.info/privacy/policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 11:21:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://salocal.info/privacy/policy/</guid>
      <description>We do not and will not assist or permit any third party to, pass information to Google that Google could use or recognize as personally identifiable information. We abide by an appropriate Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy therefore aims to ensure that a User is provided with clear and comprehensive information about, and consents to, the storing and accessing of cookies or other information on the User’s device where such activity occurs in connection with the Service and where providing such information and obtaining such consent is required by law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Renew Vehicle License Disc Online</title>
      <link>https://salocal.info/za/license/how-to-renew-car-license-disc-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 21:09:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://salocal.info/za/license/how-to-renew-car-license-disc-online/</guid>
      <description>We all know the headache of queuing at the Driving Licence Testing Centre for a car licence disc renewal. Here’s how to renew your car license disc online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Process for R350 Grant Appeal</title>
      <link>https://salocal.info/za/sassa/new-process-for-r350-grant-appeal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 22:15:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://salocal.info/za/sassa/new-process-for-r350-grant-appeal/</guid>
      <description>The requirements for the Social Relief of Distress R350 grant was recently changed. Here’s how the new appeals application process will work through ITTSA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to check status for SRD Grant</title>
      <link>https://salocal.info/za/sassa/srd-status-check/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 20:24:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://salocal.info/za/sassa/srd-status-check/</guid>
      <description>The SRD R350 grant serves as a crucial relief measure for millions of unemployed South Africans. Here&amp;rsquo;s 3 easy ways to apply for your Sassa grant online.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
